[SINGING] Designing emails can be really tough.
在設計 郵件 可真 難熬。
Client preprocessors can be pretty rough.
客戶端 預處理器 可以是相當 粗糙。
To code email for all their devices,
編寫 電子郵件 的 所有設備 ，
cut the design into many slices.
切 設計 成很多 片。
Mark it up in tables with inline style,
與 內嵌樣式 表 標記 起來 ，
with media queries into one big file.
有 媒體查詢 成一個大文件 。
To win, you'll train and learn the details —
要贏， 你會 訓練和 學習 的細節 - 。
Unmasking HTML Emails!
揭露 HTML 電子郵件！
Welcome back.
歡迎回來。
In level one, you learned how to defeat one opponent by countering the preprocessing skills of Gmail.
在level 1，你學會了如何使用對抗Gmail預處理器的技巧。
In this level, you're going to learn
在本 level， 你將了解
about multiple opponents, and their secret weapon,
更多個對手 ，以及他們的秘密武器....
the Word rendering engine.
....."Word 的 排版引擎" 。
In order to defeat them,
為了 擊敗他們 ，
we're going to be recreating our header using tables for layout.
我們將要重新設定 我們的 header 。
In this section, we're going to focus on Outlook 2003 and 2013.
在 本節中 ， 我們將 專注於 Outlook 2003和 2013 。
The reason that we're focusing on both of these
我們 專注於 這兩個的原因是
is that they use different rendering engines.
他們使用 不同的排版 引擎。
Prior to 2007, Word used Internet Explorer 6 for its rendering engine.
2007年之前 ， Word 用 的Internet Explorer 6 當它的 排版引擎 。
2007 and later uses Microsoft Word.
2007年 以後是使用Microsoft Word 。
You can see here that we get unexpected results
你可以看到 我們得到了意想不到的效果 。
when word processing software is rendering our HTML and CSS.
當使用WORD來處理HTML和CSS時 。
Our stars' width is correct,
我們的 星星圖案 寬度 是正確的，
the styles are missing from the background of it,
背景消失，
and our padding is missing from our paragraph tag.
我們的留白間格 也從段落標記後方 消失
The reason all this happens is that Word lacks box model and positioning support.
這一切 發生的是因 Word 沒有 box model 與 定位支援
Everything that you can think of that
你能想到的是
you would want to use to create a layout in CSS
你所創建要來使用的CSS
is not supported by it.
將不被他所支援。
So we can't set specific heights, display options,floats, or positions.
所以我們無法設定指定的高度、顯示選項 ，浮動 ， 或 位置 。
We do get minimal support for width and padding.
我們在寬度 和 間格 上有得到些許的支援
However, they're not supported on div element or paragraph
然而，他們不支援或的標籤。
They are, however, supported on table elements.
但他們支援 table 的元素。
You should absolutely avoid using tables for layout when building web pages.
你必須 避免使用 table 佈局 當 構建Web 頁面 。
However, they're a necessity for HTML emails because of the lack of CSS support.
然而，他們在HTML電子郵件中是必要的，因為他缺乏對CSS的支援。
Tables typically use many semantic elements to create their structure.
table 通常 使用許多 元素 來建立他們的結構。
However, this is too much code for what we need for our layouts.
然而，這樣在佈局上會有過多的程式碼。
We're going to use simplified tables,
我們將 使用簡化 的 table ，
in that we're only going to use the table element, table row element, and table cell element.
因為我們只要使用到table元素 ， tr 和 td。
Many clients apply default spacing in order to space out tables.
許多客戶端 會使用預設間距讓table保持固定距離。
We're going to need to counter this.
我們將 需要 針對 這一點。
In order to do that, we're going to use HTML attributes, border,
為了 做到這一點， 我們將 使用 HTML屬性的 border、
cell padding, and cell spacing, and set them to zero.
cell padding 和 cell spacing，並將它們設為 0。
With those set, you can see that we no longer have any space
使用這樣設定 ， 你可以看到，我們不再有任何間隙
in between our table cells.
在我們的 表格 td 之間 。
Here's an example of our simplified table with our reset attributes
這裡 是一個我們重設後 簡單 的table 例子。
, and this table is what we're going to use to contain all of the content in our email.
我們將要把電子郵件中的所有內容包含在這個table中
Because every table that we write has to have these reset attributes,
因為每次 我們 編寫 table 都必須重置這些屬性
sometimes we're going to shorten that up, like this.
有時我們要縮短.....像這樣 。
Here, we've taken all of our content from level one
在這裡 ， 我們 使用 第一章的所有內容
and put that into a table cell.
並將它放入 一個 table 裡。
We've then added a width of 600 to our table.
我們 再加入 600 寬度 的 table
As you can see, the width is being restricted to 600 pixels.
正如你 所看到的， 寬度 被 限制為 600像素 。
However, our styles are still not displaying the way that we want to.
然而 ， 我們的 style 依然 照我們想要的方式顯示 。
One example is that the background styles for our image are still not rendering properly.
其中一個例子是背景圖片的style仍然沒有正常呈現。
The Word rendering engine has very minimal support for styles on any HTML elements, except for the table and table cell.
Word的 排版引擎 除了之外對任何HTML元素 都有 非常小的 支援。
This means we need to divide our content into individual table cells that can be styled.
這意味著我們需要將您的內容轉換成單獨能夠被設定樣式的table。
Let's take a look at how this would affect our header.
讓我們來 看看這會如何影響 我們的 header 。
We can create our header as a single table with three rows,each with a single cell.
我們可以建一個table中包含三行，且每一行都是一個td。
Let's take a look at how that looks in code.
讓我們來 看看 程式碼。
The first row has a cell that contains our image,
第一行 有一個包含 我們的圖片的單元格 ，
the second row has a cell that contains our title,
第二行有一個包含你的標題的單元格，
and the third row has a cell that contains our paragraph.
和 第三行 具有一個包含 了 文字段落 的細胞。
We're not going to use the H1 and paragraph element
我們不打算 使用 H1 和段落元素，
so that we don't have to counter any styles that will be added on by clients.
所以我們 不必 克服任何在客戶端加上去的樣式設定。
Earlier, we applied our styles directly to our image tag.
早些時候 ， 我們直接將樣是設定在圖片上。
However, to get the best support
然而 ， 以獲得最佳 的支援
we want to apply our background color and padding to the table cell.
我們要應用背景顏色和留白在單元欄位上。
Now, you may wonder why we also don't move display: block and max-width: 100% up to the table cell.
現在，你可能會問，為什麼我們還沒有將display: block和max-width:100%放到table cell上。
This is because, while it wouldn't cause a problem in this example
這 是 因為 ， 雖然它 在這個例子中也不會 造成問題 。
if we were in a multi-column layout,that could break the layout in some clients.
如果我們 在多 列佈局 ，這可能會打破一些客戶端的設定。
Moving on to styling our title, this would be the same process as we did earlier,
移動style到title去，這是和前面所相同的過程。
except that we're applying all of those styles to the table cell.
除非我們要套用一樣的樣式設定到table中。
The one nice thing is, we no longer have to include reset CSS in there,
其中一個好處是 ， 我們不再需要重新設定CSS
because we're not getting any default styles applied to our cell.
因為我們 沒有被套用到任何 預設樣式 在單元欄位上。
Like before, this text has a combination of layout styles and font styles,
像之前一樣 ， 本文的布局包含了樣式設定和字體樣式。
and we're applying them all directly to the table cell.
而且我們 將 他們全部 直接 應用在表格單元中。
Like before, we're going to apply our text-align: center to our containing element,
像以前一樣，我們要應用text-align: center在本文中。
but now our containing element is a table instead.
但現在 所包含的元素是用一個表格來代替 。
You may wonder why we wouldn't bring all of our font styles up to the table level and allow them to only be set once.
你可能會 問，為什麼 我們不 把 我們所有的 字體樣式 都列到 ，讓他們只會設定一次。
Here are some examples of some
這裡 是一些 例子。
webmail clients,
網絡郵箱
and the default styles that they would set to table cells.
和會將之設置在單元表格上的預設樣式。
As we saw earlier, Gmail will actually set font family of Arial.
正如我們 前面看到的， Gmail會 實際 設定字體為 Arial。
This means that if we ever have a table cell without the font family set on it, it will default to Arial。
這 意味著， 如果我們 有一個沒有設定字體樣式的單元表格，他就會被預設為Arial。
AOL goes one step further,
AOL 更進一步 ，
in that they would set the color to black on any table cell that we do not have a color set on.
他們將 顏色設置為 黑色 在任何 我們沒有設定顏色的表格單元格。
These examples make it clear
這些例子 清楚地表明 我們 。
that we need to default to setting font styles on our table cells.
我們需要 設定字體樣式在 我們的 表格單元上。
In level one, we used margin: 0 auto
在一個層面上，我們用margin: 0 auto
in order to center our containing element.
為了使我們的元素可以置中。
Now that our containing element is a table,
現在 ，我們的 含 元素 是一個表 ，
we're going to use an HTML attribute, align,
我們將 使用HTML 屬性 ，對齊(align) ，
with a value of center.
是 中心 的值。
With that attribute applied, our table is now centered.
有了這個屬性的設定，我們的table被置中了。
The final step in recreating our header with tables is to add our background.
創建一個標頭表最後一步就是加入我們的背景。
In order to do this, we're going to wrap our container table inside of another table
為了做到這一點，我們要打包內文表格進入另一個表格中。
, and we're going to apply our background to that outer table.
而且我們將應用背景在外部table中 。
Remember, it's always important to
請記住 ， 很重要的是
continue testing how your changes affect multiple clients.
不停地測試你的修改是如何影響到客戶端的呈現。
Here, we can see that our layout is looking great in Outlook
在這裡，我們可以看到，你的版面在這邊很棒。
using Internet Explorer as a rendering engine,
當使用Internet Explorer 作為 Outlook的排版引擎時 ，
Outlook using Microsoft Word as a rendering engine,
使用Outlook Microsoft Word作為 一個 排版引擎時 ，
and Gmail using Chrome's rendering engine.
和 使用Gmail Chrome的 排版引擎 時。
There are some small differences in the font styles,
在字體樣式上有一些小的差異 ，
but we'll tackle those later.
稍後我們將 解決這些 。
Now it's your turn to recreate the header using tables for layout.
現在 輪到你 創建一個header table 來設定版面 。